Preliminary Guide to the Frank Bardacke Papers M2014
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Personal Files
  - Subseries 2.2: Personal Files
    - Wetlands, F (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Pesticides, F (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Frozen Food, F (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Radcliff Chalk Circle, F (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Frozen Food, F (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Local Reps., F (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - De Luca, F (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Earthquakes, F (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Food, F (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Cuba, F (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Logging, F (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Chicano History and Culture, F (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Local Profiles, F (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - FBD Govt, F (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Central America Curriculum, F (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Literacy, F (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Insurance, F (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Minimum Wage, F (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Plant Closures, F (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Lefters for Reagan, F (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Central America, F (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Chicanos, F (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Toxic Wastes, F (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - 200 Block, F (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Development, F (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Housing, F (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - LAs Costureras, F (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Ugarte, Alicia, F (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Fee Classes and Pro growth, F (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Health - Aging, F (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Medicare, F (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Fishing, F (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Watso, F (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Watson, F (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Police/Crime Justice - Prisons, F (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Local Business, F (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - MALDEF, F (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Subseries 3: Recent Working Files
    - Rose UFW, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Duke, Alton, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Haslan, Atlas, Central Valley Notes, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Hoover Jam, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Tomas Gonzalez Alinsky N Fund, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Historics, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Starr Endangered, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Machada, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Mexicans "Que Somos", Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Nelson-Cisneros UCAPAWA, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Farm Labor History to 1965, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Craig: Braceros, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Ann Loftus from Horbrook, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - The IS and the [Conventors], Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Dues Adjustment 1973, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Dues and Hiring Hall Problems '71, '72, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Gov't Meetings N.D., Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - 1973 County Strikes/ Strike End, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - White River Farms Chronology, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Coachella Negotiation with terms 1972-73, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Julio Hernandez to Cesar, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Boycott 1971, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Plan of Delano, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - 1973 La Paz, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Inter Haverst/Cesar, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Gallo, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Harrisburg 8, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Cesar Mendez Pilot, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Giumarra Time Line '65-'68, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Fast/Pledges, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - (Velasco) 1969 Coachella Grape Strike, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Melon Strike 1970, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Dues Check Off, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Strawberry Strike Salinas '73, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - Si Se Puede, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - Giumarra Negotiations 1973, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - Blythe Bus, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - Alatore - '73 States/Team Answer, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - 1974 IS, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - Bobby Kennedy, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - UFW Farmers (1967-74), Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 47)
    - AG Land Values, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - Short Handled Hoe, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - Wage Surveys 1989, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 50)
    - Union Democracy, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 51)
    - Celery Production, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 52)
    - Populations Statistics, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 53)
    - Inevitability, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 54)
    - Harvey Richards, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 55)
    - Union Theory II, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 56)
    - Union Theory Nutte Newell, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 57)
    - Bus to Border and Branch, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 58)
    - Union Theory, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 59)
    - Texas Farmworker and Illegals, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 60)
    - Bruce Perry, Black Cabinet Bottom shelf (Box 43, Folder 61)
    - Beinke Notes, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 62)
    - Miriam Admen, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 63)
    - Miriam Pawell, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 64)
    - Miriam on Dolores, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 65)
    - Miriam on Arizmendi, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 66)
    - Miriam on..., Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 67)
    - Miriam Powell, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 68)
    - Brown, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 69)
    - Prologue 3/09, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 70)
    - The Territory 3/09, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 71)
    - The Work Itseld 3/09, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 72)
    - Childhood As Destiny 3/09, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 73)
    - Lay Catholic Activist, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 74)
    - Lay Catholic Activist, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 75)
    - The Alchemist, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 76)
    - The Alchemist, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 77)
    - The Organizer in Oxnard, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 78)
    - The River's Source, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 79)
    - Family JA Edit, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 80)
    - New Wings JA Edit, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 81)
    - Boycott, Baby, Boycott JA Edit, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 82)
    - The Grape Strike JA Edit, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 83)
    - Boycott, Baby, Boycott JA Edit, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 84)
    - Granz and Regroups JA Edit, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 85)
    - The Spring Pilgrimage, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 86)
    - Battle Theater JA Edit, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 87)
    - Digiorgio JA Edit, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 88)
    - Cutting Back Jar, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 89)
    - The First Jar, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 90)
    - Triumph of Will Jar, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 91)
    - Salinas before the Storm, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 92)
    - Salinas before storm, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 93)
    - Red Lettuce Alone, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 94)
    - Up on the Mountain, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 95)
    - Goons, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 96)
    - The Grand Concession, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 97)
    - The Wet Line, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 98)
    - Living with the Law, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 43, Folder 99)
    - The Game, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - The Union in its own, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - The Last Great Strike, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Esta Huelga esta Ganada, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Victory in Hand, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Exeunt Omnes, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Civil War, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Epilogues, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Endnotes Edits, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Todd, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Chicano/a Latino/a History CSU Monterey Bay Roster, Beige Cabinet bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Chicano/a Latino/a History CSU Monterey Bay Student's Essays, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Chicano/a Latino/a History CSU Monterey Bay Student's Essays, Beige Cabinet top Shelf (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Chicano/a Latino/a History CSU Monterey Bay Student's Essays, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Chicano/a Latino/a History CSU Monterey Bay Student's Essays, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Independent Study Agreement Hector Serrato, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Eric Garcetti article, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - The 2010 Census Questionnaire: Seven Questions for Everyone, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Hispanics: Race, Class, or Ethnicity? By Margarita B. Melville, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - The Historical Society of Southern California, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Guns, Germs, and Steel, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - John O'Sullivan Declares "Boundless Future" Is America's "Manifest Destiny", Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Sal Castro and Chicano Educational Justice, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Cesar Chavez The Serpent and the Dove by Frank Bardacke, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - The Bracero Experience in Fiction, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - The Bracero Experience in Fiction, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Herold: Naming a School after Tiburcio Vasquez is folly, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Tiburcio Vasquez School in California Named after Bandido Ignites Controvery, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - "Revenge took posession of me" Tiburcio Vasquez 1874 Joaquin Murrietta 1854, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - The Historical Society of Southern California, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - The Historical Society of Southern California, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - The Historical Society of Southern California, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - The Historical Society of Southern California, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Material, Beige Cabinet Bottom Shelf (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Tapes 3/77, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Tapes 3/77, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - 3/11/79 NEB, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Hartnell Meeting, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - FWSC Various CDs, La Paz Tapes; audiocassette (Box 44, Folder 39)
- Series 3: United Farm Workers
  - Subseries 3.1: UFW [Bardecke Notes]
    - Pd Rep Trial, 6 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Cleofas Accident, 6 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Replacements for... July 81, 6 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Complaint Against Mojics 12/20/81, 6 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - #'s and Contents 79-06, 6 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Grower Exchange/Clout, 6 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Civil War/Notes, 6 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - 1988 Cancer Clusters, 6 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - 1988 Fast, 6 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Kim Notley, 6 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Teamster's in Fields 1985, 6 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Freedman, 6 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Karina Reyes, 6 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Abbatti and Andrews, 6 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - 1985 Legal Rept on Ig Ind, 6 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Perspective Heald 1985, 6 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - 85 - '86 Marketing, 6 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Cost Center, Aug 82, 6 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Strike Fund To Boycott 1982, 6 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - 1983 Approved Reps, 6 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - 1983 Revenue Boycott, 6 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - 1984 Convention, 6 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - 1983 Misc., 6 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - [Son Harvet Pullouts], 6 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - More Clips..., 6 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - 8/23/2014, 6 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Bakersfield, California 04, 6 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Legal Explanation w/ rep care, 6 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - PD Reps Legal Report 82, 6 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - PD Reps Apology 1, 6 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Sacramento Bee Fields of Betrayel 1992, 6 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - San Jose Mercury News 2000, 6 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Coastal Growers Assocation, 6 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Time Lines, 6 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Alan Lon "Family Business", 6 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Cirs Lib, 6 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Film Worker Conditions, 6 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - MAJKA: Seeline 1993, 6 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - First Time Thru, 6 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - 1983 - The End, 6 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Clips, 6 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - 1980, 6 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - The End, 6 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - ALRB 1980's, 6 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Gourmet/Grievance 1982, 6 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Abmiral/Grievance 1983/No Content, 6 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Admiral Arbitration, 6 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Mann Packing, 6 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Grower/Shipper Salinas 1981, 6 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Off The Wall, 6 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - NY Times: Farm Worker Conditions 1997, 6 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Oshita Arbitration, 6 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Movement Intities June 30, 81, 6 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Ivan/Gonzalez and Cano, 6 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - UFW Post '87, 6 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Mack Jones Case, 6 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Structure of Cal 1950-2000, 6 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Community 1983-85, 6 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Cesar in Senator (Pen in hand) Feb 1983, 6 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Food Group 1983, 6 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - 1988 Fast (See 88 Clips), 6 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Cancer Cluster, 6 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Wrath of Grapes, 6 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - 82 Contributions/Clothing, 6 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Food and Justice, 6 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Villarejo and Wells Arla, 6 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Bertuccio Alarb Settlement, 6 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Menlo College Dolors Villarejo Johnson, 6 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - 85 [Pertr...], 6 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - CRLA Elections - Post Pungo, 6 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Church Verdict 1993, 6 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Agriculture, 6 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Z Mag 1991 - Rest. Children, 6 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Cesar's Death, 6 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Washington State Contract, 6 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - 2005 [Grumaryen] Election, 6 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Marc Cooper Aug 2005, 6 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - 2007 Ag Mover in Mexico, 6 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Lettuce 1978-83, 6 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Delano G, 6 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Maggie Trial, 6 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - 1987 Salinas Negotiations, 6 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Arizon Cultural Case Cesar Dies, 6 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - IRCA and Immigration, 6 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Jessica Padilla Forced out of CRLA, 6 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Sacramento Bee 74, 6 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Tomato Acreage and Yield, 6 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - LA Times 1991, 6 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Magic Sanchez Settlement, 6 (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - ALRB Cases, 6 (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Land Values and Labor and ALRA, 6 (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Value w/ Ag Land Schilling, 6 (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Overall Farm Economy, 6 (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Imperial Valley vs Infection Rotting average, 6 (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - Runston Notes/Farms Wages Over Time, 6 (Box 21, Folder 67)
    - Rene Lopez Murder 1983, 6 (Box 21, Folder 68)
    - Closures, 6 (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - West Coast 1985 and Ulton Closures, 6 (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - Ivette [Riching] 81-82, 6 (Box 21, Folder 71)
    - Gourmet Closure 1985 Contracts, 6 (Box 21, Folder 72)
    - 1985 Contracts, 6 (Box 21, Folder 73)
    - Wrath of Grapes/Grape Boycott, 6 (Box 21, Folder 74)
    - Watsonville Contracts 1983, 6 (Box 21, Folder 75)
    - Cesar to R and F Negotiations on Infiltration, 7 (Box 21, Folder 76)
    - Answer to Higgins Oct 81 and Higgins to Cesar Sept 81, 7 (Box 21, Folder 77)
    - Renteria Statement 8/23/19, 7 (Box 21, Folder 78)
    - "We are the Chi Chi", 7 (Box 21, Folder 79)
    - Coachella 77 (Adar), 7 (Box 21, Folder 80)
    - Staff List 7/13/81, 7 (Box 21, Folder 81)
    - Imperial Meet CC and Other Consequences, 7 (Box 21, Folder 82)
    - Civil War/Notes, 7 (Box 21, Folder 83)
    - The Civil War, 7 (Box 21, Folder 84)
    - NEB 79-80, 7 (Box 21, Folder 85)
    - 1981 Convention/Delegate Ruler Reports, 7 (Box 21, Folder 86)
    - 1981 Contribution Resolutions and my notes, 7 (Box 21, Folder 87)
    - NEB '81, 7 (Box 21, Folder 88)
    - Sabino Lopez, 7 (Box 21, Folder 89)
    - NY Times, Dec. 6, 1981, 7 (Box 21, Folder 90)
    - New NEB Appointments 7/8/81, 7 (Box 21, Folder 91)
    - Left Comment on UFW, 7 (Box 21, Folder 92)
    - Trial of Mondragon 8/22/81, 7 (Box 21, Folder 93)
    - Junta Grave 6/81, 7 (Box 21, Folder 94)
    - RFR Problems 2/81, 7 (Box 21, Folder 95)
    - Cesar on 1980 Negot, 7 (Box 21, Folder 96)
    - Oscar and Busses, 7 (Box 21, Folder 97)
    - "Union Politics" 5/30/81, 7 (Box 21, Folder 98)
    - Sister Florence Zwober, 7 (Box 21, Folder 99)
    - NEB Trial Mondaagon 2/6/82, 7 (Box 21, Folder 100)
    - Jose Renteria to CC Ranch Committees 8/25/81, 7 (Box 21, Folder 101)
    - Bernstein 1981 Why didn't Oct 25th UFW Burgoon, 7 (Box 21, Folder 102)
    - Perez and Guttierrez vs Cesar, 7 (Box 21, Folder 103)
    - Field Office Needs 10/81, 7 (Box 21, Folder 104)
    - 1980 Gilroy Strikes, 7 (Box 21, Folder 105)
    - Notes of Civil War, 7 (Box 21, Folder 106)
    - Garlic Clip Notes 1950, 7 (Box 21, Folder 107)
    - Brown Sum Up Late 1981, 7 (Box 21, Folder 108)
    - Valdora/Coachella/Subcontracting, 7 (Box 21, Folder 109)
    - Sam Andrews Negotiations, 7 (Box 21, Folder 110)
    - WS Journal 5/17/82, 7 (Box 21, Folder 111)
    - Political Contributions, 7 (Box 21, Folder 112)
    - [Partial ent of SRL], 7 (Box 21, Folder 113)
    - Ranch Committee 1980, 7 (Box 21, Folder 114)
    - F.W. Conditions, 7 (Box 21, Folder 115)
    - Berry Price Rates '82, 7 (Box 21, Folder 116)
    - Church, 7 (Box 21, Folder 117)
    - Farm Report Murder in Green Field 1981, 7 (Box 21, Folder 118)
    - Complaint to Cesar from Workers 1982, 7 (Box 21, Folder 119)
    - Bissom, 7 (Box 21, Folder 120)
    - 1982 Cesar "Ni de la Responsabilidad", 7 (Box 21, Folder 121)
    - Newsweek 1981, 7 (Box 21, Folder 122)
    - Maricopia C.O.P. UFW 1980, 7 (Box 21, Folder 123)
    - Intern Harvest Quality of Pack Seniority, 7 (Box 21, Folder 124)
    - Siegel/Radical Wrecker, 7 (Box 21, Folder 125)
    - Strike Insurance, 7 (Box 21, Folder 126)
    - What New and Old Arguments, 7 (Box 21, Folder 127)
    - 1966-1971, 7 (Box 21, Folder 128)
    - Cesar Misc., 7 (Box 21, Folder 129)
    - Meanwhile back in the Farm, 7 (Box 21, Folder 130)
    - Abbie Robideaux, 7 (Box 21, Folder 131)
    - Wayne State 06 II, 7 (Box 21, Folder 132)
    - Anna Violich, 7 (Box 21, Folder 133)
    - Wayne State Notes 1st 1997, 7 (Box 21, Folder 134)
    - Wayne State 06 I, 7 (Box 21, Folder 135)
    - Beineke, 7 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Beineke, 7 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Latino Oct 79 Dec 82, 7 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - CPD 1979, 7 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Contracts 1978, 7 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Beineke, 7 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - RFF Medical/Tax Returns Auditions Report, 7 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Health Plan, 7 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Legal Dept. 77, 7 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Paid Rep Plans B, 7 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Paid Reps, 7 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Paid Reps I, 7 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - The Fast, 7 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - ALRB Library Notes and Selections, 7 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Untitled Folder, 7 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 3.2: UFW Files
    - IRS 990's, 11 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Umon Dubs/Revenues, 11 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Citicards, 11 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - The Service Center is the Financial Hub, 11 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Nat'l Farm Workers Health Group, 11 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - "The Tail Now Wags the Dog", 11 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - The Service Center, 11 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Stony Brook Corporation, 11 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - The LM2's are for the reunion itself. Get from U.S. Dept. of Labor, 11 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - The Service Center, 11 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - National Farm workers Service Center, 11 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Martin Luther King Farm Worker Fund, 11 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Radio Campesina, 11 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - RFK Medical Plan, 11 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Farm Workers Communications, Inc, 11 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Farm Workers Corporation, 11 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Credit Union, 11 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Farm Workers Credit Union, 11 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Pension Fund his Managed, 11 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Juan de La Cruz Fund, 11 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Farmworkers Education Leadership Development, 11 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Cesar E. Chavez Foundation, 11 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Cesar E. Chavez Community Development Fund, 11 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Citizenship Participation Day Fund, 11 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Justification for "Non-Profit" "Entities", 11 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - David Martinez Portrait, 11 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - American Liberty Investments, 11 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - UFW Subsidiaries, 11 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Request for Public Inspection, 11 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - People who Research Sacramento Documents, 11 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Department of Insurance, 11 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Calif. Registry of Charitable Trusts, 11 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Form C-2, 11 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Fresno Real Estate (UFW), 11 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Notes, 11 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Empty Folder, 11 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - How to Search for UFW, 11 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Value of Fresno Real Estate, 11 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - 1989 Riverbank Enterprise, 11 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Riverside Press - Enterprise, 11 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Properties Owned by UFW (Real Estate), 11 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Notes, 11 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Labor Organization Annual Report, 11 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Labor Organization Annual Report, 11 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - United Farm Workers of America, 11 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Subseries 3.3: UFW Tax Documents
    - Registration Form (1 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Registration Form (2 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Registration Form (3 of 3), 12 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 12 (Box 25, Folder 39)